Guide to the Richard Pollay. Tobacco industry promotion (TIPS) collection, 1885-2012 and undated RL.11612
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- 950. Print Advertising, 1906-2006; undated; 3
  - Small Format, 1906-2006; undated; 1
    - Minor brands--S-Y, 1930-1998 (Box 11)
      Includes, Sterling, Stride, Style, Tall, Tempo, Triumph, True, Twenty Grand, Twist, USA, Viceroy, Virginia Rounds, Waterford, White Owl, Wings, York
    - Corporate advertising, 1945-2001 (Box 11)
      Includes pamphlets collected at tours or tobacco companies
    - Industry-sponsored anti-smoking campaigns, 1985-2003 (Box 11)
    - Outdoor advertising, 1999; undated (Box 11)
    - Solicitations to smoke, 1933-1985 (Box 11)
    - Smoker surveys and direct mail, 1990-2000 (Box 11)
    - Smoking advocacy (Smokers' rights, etc.), 1959-1999; 4 folders (Box 11)
    - Tobacco industry sponsorship (events, sports, etc.), 1988-2000 (Box 11)
  - Large Format, 1914-2002; undated; 2
    - Benson & Hedges, 1970-1995 (Box 12)
    - Camel, 1919-1929 (Box 12)
    - Camel, 1930s (Box 13)
    - Camel, 1940s (Box 13a)
    - Camel, 1950-2000 (Box 13b)
    - Carlton, 1963-1984 (Box 14)
    - Chesterfield, 1929-1949 (Box 14)
    - Chesterfield, 1950-1960s (Box 14a)
    - Kent, 1953-1980 (Box 14a)
    - Kool, 1934-1999 (Box 15)
    - L&M, 1954-1978 (Box 15)
    - Lark, 1963-1972 (Box 16)
    - Lucky Strike, 1927-1930s (Box 16)
    - Lucky Strike, 1930-1969 (Box 16a)
    - Lucky Strike, 1970-2000 (Box 17)
    - Marlboro, 1927-1969 (Box 17)
    - Marlboro, 1960-1989 (Box 17a)
    - Marlboro, 1990-2000 (Box 18)
    - Maryland, Merit, 1976-2000 (Box 18)
    - Newport, 1959-2000 (Box 18)
    - Old Gold, 1930-1972 (Box 18a)
    - Pall Mall, 1924-1972 (Box 19)
    - Parliament, 1955-2001 (Box 19)
    - Philip Morris, 1938-1966 (Box 19a)
    - Salem, 1956-2000 (Box 20)
    - Tareyton, 1950-1972 (Box 20)
    - Vantage, 1971-1989 (Box 20a)
    - Velvet, 1922 (Box 20a)
    - Viceroy, 1947-1979 (Box 20a)
    - Virginia Slims, 1968-2000 (Box 21)
    - Winston, 1951-2000 (Box 21)
    - Minor brands A-G, 1929-2002; undated (Box 21a)
      Includes Adam, All American, American Spirit, Antonio & Cleopatra, Barclay, Basic, Belair, Brandon, Bucks, Bull Durham, Cambridge, Capri, Century, Chelsea, Dave's, Dunhill, Doral, Duke, Embassy, Encore, Eric, Eve, Fatima, Fleetwood, Galaxy/Alpine, Golden Lights
    - Minor brands H-R, 1914-2002; undated (Box 22)
      Includes Half and Half, Hit Parade, Iceberg, Julep, Kamel, King Sano, Life, Listerine, Magna, Maryland, Masterpiece, Misty, Montclair, Moonlight, More, Multifilter, Murad, New Leaf, Next, Now, Oasis, Omar, Omni, Players, Pyramid, Raleigh, Ramses, Regent, Rooster, Samson, Sano, Silva Thins, Skoal, Spring, Spud, Tempo, Tennyson, Triumph, True,Turkey Red, Tuxedo, White Owl, York
    - Minor brands S-Y, 1914-2002 and undated (Box 22a)
    - Miscellaneous, 1939-2000 (Box 22a)
      Includes contests, industry promotions, anti-smoking campaigns
- 1000. Advertising and Marketing, 1937-2006; undated; 4
  - 1001. Cigarette advertising in medical journals, 1940-1955; 3
    - Contents of binder, 1940-1955; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - 1002. Cigarette advertising in nursing journals, 1940-1956; 4
    - Contents of binder, 1940-1956; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - 1003. Overseas Marketing of Tobacco (Working papers and sources), 1980-1995; 5
    - Contents of binder of articles, 1980-1995; 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Contents of binder of articles, 1992-1995 (Box 24)
    - Contents of binder of unprocessed tobacco articles, 1984-1995 (Box 24)
    - International Promotion of Cigarettes: An Annotated Bibliography, Richard Pollay and David Carter-Whitney, 1990 (Box 24)
    - Promotion of Cigarettes Overseas: An Annotated Bibliography. WP95.4. Richard Pollay and Robin Ritchie, 1995 (Box 24)
    - The Empire Strikes Back: Responses of the Global Tobacco Industry to the Decline of Traditional Markets. WP95.3. Robin Ritchie, 1995 (Box 24)
  - 1004. Overseas Advertising and Promotion, 1989-2006; undated; 6
    - Effect of Tobacco Advertising on Tobacco Consumption (U.K.), 1992 (Box 24)
    - GASP Smoke Free Solutions (U.K.)--Catalog, 2006 (Box 24)
    - Health or Tobacco: An End to Tobacco Advertising and Promotion (New Zealand), 1989 (Box 24)
    - International Trade--Advertising and Promoting U.S. Cigarettes in Selected Asian Countries, 1992 (Box 24)
    - Introduction to International Trade Agreements and Their Impact on Public Measures to Reduce Tobacco Use (Canada/U.K.), 2001 (Box 24)
    - Pushing Smoke: Tobacco Advertising and Promotion (WHO/Denmark), undated (Box 24)
    - Towards a Europe Free from Tobacco Advertising (WHO Denmark/Finland), 1991 (Box 24)
  - 1005. Cigarette Advertising in Canada, 1966-2005; 7
    - Backgrounder: Tobacco on Trial Project, 1990 (Box 24)
    - Bill C-51 (Tobacco Products Control Act)--Articles about tobacco regulation in other countries, 1983-1987 (Box 24)
    - Bill C-51 (Tobacco Products Control Act)--Clippings and articles, 1987-1990; 3 folders (Box 25)
    - Bill C-51 (Tobacco Products Control Act)--Statements and testimony, 1987-1988; 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Bill C-51 (Tobacco Products Control Act)--Statements and testimony, 1987-1988 (Box OV3)
    - Bill C-51 and Bill C-204 (Non-Smokers Health Act) debates, 1988 (Box 25)
    - Bill-C71 (Tobacco Act, regulating tobacco packaging and marketing), 1996-1997; 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Bill C-204: Stan Buda (Ted Bates) Submission to the Legislative Committee, 1987 (Box 25)
    - Break Free: Directional Paper of the National Program to Reduce Tobacco Use in Canada, 1987 (Box 25)
    - Cynthia Callard et al: Curing the Addiction to Profits, 2005 (Box 25)
    - Examination of the Factors Influencing Juvenile Smoking Initiation in Canada, 1987 (Box 26)
    - FTC (Federal Trade Commission)--Petition for Regulation of Unfair and Deceptive Alcoholic Beverage Advertising and Marketing Practices, 1985 (Box 26)
    - Gallup--Attitudes Toward Smoking Restrictions, 1987 (Box 26)
    - Health Canada Concept Testing, 1998 (Box 26)
    - House of Commons Standing Order 108(2): Plain Packaging of Tobacco Products, 1994 (Box 26)
    - Info-Tabac: Newsletter for a Tobacco-Free Quebec, 2005 (Box 26)
    - J.J. Boddewyn: Tobacco Advertising in a Free Society, 1986 (Box OV3)
    - Jacques Cole: Tobacco Ads UK: No Words, Logos, Models, Brands or Packages, 1989 (Box 26)
    - John Luik (Niagara Institute) articles, 1988-1997 (Box 26)
    - Maureen Baker: Tobacco Smoking, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Mealey's Litigation Reports: Tobacco, 1988 (Box 26)
    - Michael Waterson: Expert Witness Statement, circa 1988 (Box 26)
    - National Survey of the Behaviour, Knowledge and Attitudes of Canadians Regarding Cancer, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Neil Collishaw articles and papers, 1987 (Box 26)
    - Non-Smokers Rights Association, 1984-1989 (Box 26)
    - Non-Smokers Rights Association--David Sweanor: Response to Charter of Rights Arguments Against the Tobacco Products Control Act, 1988 (Box 26)
    - Non-Smokers Rights Association--Give Kids a Chance, 1987 (Box 26)
    - Ontario Tobacco Research Unit directory, 2004 (Box 26)
    - Putting Health First: The Case for Plain Packaging of Tobacco Products, 1994 (Box 27)
    - Randy Woods: Tobacco Sponsorship Advertising in the Ottawa/Hull Region, 1993 (Box 27)
    - Regina v. Imperial Tobacco, 1972 (Box 27)
    - Report on Tobacco and Cigarette Smoking, 1974 (Box 27)
    - Richard Pollay: Information and Imagery in Contemporary Canadian Cigarette Ads, 1990 (Box 27)
    - Richard Pollay, Anne Lavack: Targeting of Youths by Cigarette Makers, 1993 (Box 27)
    - Smoking and Public Policy in Canada, 1988 (Box 27)
    - Statistics, 1986-1989 (Box 27)
    - Study of Cigarette Advertising, Manitoba, 1966 (Box 27)
    - Tobacco Industry Voluntary Packaging and Advertising Code, 1995 (Box 27)
    - Towards Zero Consumption: Generic Packaging of Tobacco Products, 1994 (Box 27)
    - When Packages Can't Speak: Possible Impacts of Plain and Generic Packaging of Tobacco Products, 1995 (Box 27)
  - 1006. Cigarette Advertising and Articles in Time, Life, 1942-1979; 8
    - Contents of binder (photocopies), 1942-1979 (Box 27)
    - Contents of binder (photocopies), 1942-1979; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Loose advertisements--Beechnut, 1942 (Box OV3)
    - Loose advertisements--Camel, 1937-1947; 2 folders (Box OV3)
    - Loose advertisements--Chelsea, 1941-1946 (Box OV3)
    - Loose advertisements--Chesterfield, 1937-1947 (Box OV3)
    - Loose advertisements--Domino, 1941-1942 (Box OV3)
    - Loose advertisements--Kool, 1937-1941 (Box OV3)
    - Loose advertisements--Lucky Strike, 1937-1947; 2 folders (Box OV3)
    - Loose advertisements--Old Gold, 1938-1946 (Box OV3)
    - Loose advertisements--Pall Mall, 1937-1947 (Box OV3)
    - Loose advertisements--Philip Morris, 1939-1947 (Box OV3)
    - Loose advertisements--Regent, 1940-1946 (Box OV3)
    - Loose advertisements--Spud, 1939-1943 (Box OV3)
    - Loose advertisements--Other brands, 1937-1947 (Box OV3)
  - 1007. Cigarette Advertising in Ebony, 1950-1964; 9
    - Contents of binder (photocopies), 1950-1964 (Box 28)
    - Photocopies of advertisements, 1950-1964; 2 folders (Box OV3)
  - 1008. Sixty Years of Deception: An Analysis and Compilation of Cigarette Advertisements 1925-1985 (Health Advocacy Center), 1986; 10
    - Volume 1: 1925-1939, 1986; 3 folders (Box 28)
    - Volume 2: 1940-1953, 1986 (Box 28)
    - Volume 2: 1940-1953, 1986; 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Volume 3: 1954-1963, 1986; 3 folders (Box 29)
    - Volume 4: 1964-1968, 1986; 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Volume 5: 1969-1973, 1986; 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Volume 6: Black and Hispanic ads (English and Spanish), 1986; 4 folders (Box 30)
  - 1009. Advertising Professionals on Cigarette Advertising Regulation, 1996-2001; 11
    - Contents of binder of clippings, 1996-2001 (Box 30)
  - 1011. Media Campaign Resource Center, 12
    - Resource Book for Tobacco Control vol. 2, 1998 (Box 31)
  - 1012. Ad Smarts (Scott Newman Center: Preventing Drug Abuse Through Education for the Promotion of Health and Media Education, 1993; 13
    - Module A: Media and Advertising, 1993 (Box 31)
    - Module B: Alcohol Advertising, 1993 (Box 31)
    - Module C: Tobacco Advertising, 1993 (Box 31)
    - Module D: Media, Tobacco and Alcohol Advertising, 1993 (Box 31)
    - Module E: Media Action, 1993 (Box 31)
  - 1034. Tobacco Reporter, 1995-2003; 14
    - Selection of issues, 1995-2003; 5 folders (Box 32)
  - 1035. Tobacco Control: An International Journal, 1992-2006; 15
    - Vol. 1 through Vol. 8, 1992-1999; 8 folders (Box 32)
    - Vol. 9 through Vol. 12, 2000-2003; 4 folders (Box 33)
    - Vol. 12 through Vol. 15, 2003-2006; 4 folders (Box 34)
  - 1036. Tobacco Advertising in Life Magazine, 1953-2000; 16
    - Contents of binder: Index to advertisements in Life, 2000 (Box 34)
- 2000. Pollay Publications and History of Advertising Archives Working Papers, 1922-2006; undated; 5
  - 2001. Richard Pollay Publications, 1985-2006; 17
    - Chronological notes on cigarette advertising history, 1985-1997; 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Cigarette publications binder Vol. 1, 1990-1994; 2 folders (Box 35)
      Propaganda, Puffing and the Public Interest (1990); The Major Minor Issue: Children, Cigarettes and Advertising Self-Regulation in the Sixties (1993); The Changing Character of American Cigarette Advertising (1993); Tricks of the Tobacco Trade (1993); Cigarette Advertising Pertinent Research and Impertinent Opinions: Our Contributions to the Cigarette Advertising Policy Debate (1993); Sifting the Ashes: An Intellectual History of Cigarette Advertising Research (1994); Consumer Reports on Cigarettes 1936-1993 (1994); Advertising Issues in the Tobacco Journals 1950-1954 (1994); As Anyone Can Plainly See: Brand Imagery in Cigarette Packaging and Promotion (1994); Stop and Think! Consider this before yo develop retail cigarette warnings (1994); Kids, Baseball and the Marlboro Man (1994); Printers Ink and Tobacco Tar 1964-1970 (1994); Advertising Issues in the Tobacco Journals 1955-1959 (1994)
    - Cigarette publications binder Vol. 2, 1990-1991 (Box 35)
      Black and White and Read All Over: Cigarette Advertising in Ebony and Life 1950-1965 (1990); Cigarette Health Risk Misconceptions Among Americans and Canadians (1990); The Functions and Management of Cigarette Advertising (1991); Information and Imagery in Contemporary Canadian Cigarette Ads; Propaganda, Puffing and the Public Interest (1990); The More Things Change (1991)
    - Cigarette publications binder Vol. 3, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box 35)
      Blowing Away the Smoke Screen: A Few of the Tobacco Industry's Yellow Lies (1991); Signs and Symbolism in American Cigarette Advertising: A Historical Analysis of the Use of "Pictures of Health" (1991); Cigarette Ad Exposure to Youth: TV Use under Self-Regulation 1963 (1992); HIstorical Content Analysis of Cigarette Advertising (1992); Separate, but Not Equal: Racial Segmentation in Cigarette Advertising (1992); Printers Ink and Tobacco Tar 1955-1959 (1993); Printers Ink and Tobacco Tar 1950-1954 (1993); Cigarette Advertising and Life 1937-1947 (1993); Printers Ink and Tobacco Tar 1960-1963 (1993); Getting Good and Being Super Bad: Chapters in the Prmotion of Cigarettes to Blacks (1993); The Targeting of Youths by Cigarette Marketers: Archival Evidence on Trial (1993)
    - Cigarette publications binder Vol. 4, 1987-1990 (Box 35)
      Themes and Tactics in Cigarette Advertising 1938-1983: Technical Report on Methods and Measures (1987); Tracking the Marlboro Man, Speedy Alka-Seltzer, and the Pepsi Generation Through the Smithsonian Archives (1987); Getting Away with Murder: Cigarette Advertising to Take Your Breath Away (1988); Promotion and Policy for a Pandemic Product: Notes on the History of Cigarette Advertising (1988); On Misleading Studies "Proving" that Cigarette Ad Bans Don't Work (1989); Filters, Flavor, Flim-Flam, too! On "Health Information" and Policy Implications in Cigarette Advertising (1989); More Chronological Notes on the Promotion of Cigarettes (1990); International Promotion of Cigarettes: An Annotated Bibliography (1990)
    - Cigarette publications binder Vol. 4, 1987-1990 (Box 36)
    - Cigarette publications binder Vol. 5, 1994; 2 folders (Box 36)
      Recommendations for a British Colombia Tobacco Control Strategy (1994); Advertising and Selling the Tobacco Industry 1948-1953 (1994); Advertising and Selling the Tobacco Industry 1954-1958 (1994); Printers Ink and Tobacco Tar 1933-1949 (1994); Advertising Issues in the Tobacco Journals 1960-1962 (1994); Targeting the Young Is an Old Story: A History of Cigarette Advertising to the Young (1994); Preventing Tobacco Use Among Young People (1994); Exposure of U.S. Youth to Cigarette Television Advertising in the 1960s (1994); Advertising Issues in the Tobacco Journals 1963-1965 (1994); The Cowboy and Genital Joe (1994)
    - Cigarette publications binder Vol. 6, 1994-1995; 2 folders (Box 36)
      Tricks of the Tobacco Trade (1995); Readers Digest's Ingestion of Tobacco 1924-1994 (1995); Cigarette Advertising and Marketing Strategies: How this Information Can Be Used in Litigation (1994); Transnational Firms vs. State Monopolies: Lessons in Competitiveness from Marlboro Country (1995); Thoughtless Persuasion: Cigarette Advertising to Minimize Cognitive Processing and Counter-arguments (1995); Targeting Tactics in Selling Smoke: Youthful Aspects of 20th Century Cigarette Advertising (1995); "Below the Belt" Cigarette Advertising (1995); Promotion of Cigarettes Overseas: An Annotated Bibliography (1995); You've Come the Wrong Way, Baby! Chapters in the Continuing Saga of Cigarette Advertising Targeting Women (1995); Chronological Notes re: Kent Cigarettes 1952-1959 (1995)
    - Cigarette publications binder Vol. 7, 1995-1996 (Box 36)
      The Empire Strikes Back: Responses of the Global Tobacco Industry to the Decline of Traditional Markets (1995); Dressed to Kill in Suits and Lies (1996); Primary Goal Clearly to Hook Teens (1995); Re: Lifestyle Advertising for Cigarettes (1995); Separate But Not Equal: Racial Segmentation in Cigarette Advertising (1992); The BUZ in Canada without an ad ban (1995); Realized Market Share among Old and New Smokers and Advertising Share of Voice (1996); Cigarette Advertising and Realized Market Share among Mature and Immature Smokers (1996); The Last Straw? Cigarette Advertising and Realized Market Shares Among Youths and Adults, 1979-1993 (1996); Pretty Pictures and a Pack of Lies: Understanding How Cigarette Advertising and Promotion Works (1996); Be Un-Happy, Go Luckies: Notes on Lucky Strike Advertising with special emphasis on 1950-1965 (1996); Deadly Targeting of Women in Promoting Cigarettes (1996); Advertising and Promotion Programs (1996); It's No Accident: Tobacco Advertising Attracts Youth; Unfairly Sublime or Fairly Ridiculous: On "Crotch Canyon," "Genital Joe" Camel and other Below the Belt Cigarette Ads (1997)
    - Cigarette publications binder Vol. 8, 1997-1999; 2 folders (Box 36)
      Unfairly Sublime or Fairly Ridiculous: On "Crotch Canyon," "Genital Joe" Camel and other Below the Belt Cigarette Ads (1997); Reality Checks: Counter-Advertising Lessons From Trade Practices (1997); Hacks, Flacks and Counter-attacks: Cigarette Advertising, Sponsored Research, and Controversies (1997); Tobacco Marketing Targets Youth (1997); Flaws and Fallacies of Proposed Congressional Cigarette "Settlement"; Is Outdoor Advertising FAIR to Children? (1998); Publicly Visible Cigarette Advertising (1998); Tobacco Use among U.S. Racial/Ethnic Minority Groups; Tricks of the Tobacco Trade (1998); How Cigarette Advertising Works in the Courtroom: Lessons from Litigation (1999); Successful Images and Failed Fact: The Dark Side of Marketing Seemingly Light Cigarettes (1999)
    - Cigarette publications binder Vol. 9, 2000-2001 (Box 37)
      Targeting youth and concerned smokers: evidence from Canadian tobacco industry documents (2000); Export "A" ads are extremely expert, eh? (2001); Sifting the Ashes: Understanding Cigarette Marketing Through Historical and Archival Research (2001); Marketing Cigarettes with Low Machine-Measured Yields; Content Analysis of Cigarette Advertising: A Critical Review of the Literature; Marketing to Youth: Evidence from Corporate Documents (2001); Exposing Mr. Butts' Tricks of the Trade; The Dark Side of Marketing Seemingly "Light" Cigarettes: Successful Images and Failed Fact
    - Cigarette publications binder Vol. 10, 1990-1998; 2 folders (Box 37)
      Propaganda, Puffing and the Public Interest (1990); The Unscientific Perspective of the Tobacco Industry Research Committee 1954 (1998); Exposure of U.S. Youth to Cigarette Television Advertising in the 1960s (1994); Separate but not Equal: Racial Segmentation in Cigarette Advertising (1992); Preventing Tobacco Use Among Young People (1994); Promises, promises: self-regulation of US cigarette broadcast advertising in the 1960s (1994); Targeting of Youths by Cigarette Marketers: Archival Evidence on Trial (1993); "Below the Belt" cigarette advertising; NIcotine Addiction is a Deadly Pediatric Disease (1994); Deadly Targeting of Women in Promoting Cigarettes (1996); Targeting Tactics in Selling Smoke: Youthful Aspects of 20th Century Cigarette Advertising (1995); The Last Straw? Cigarette Advertising and Realized Market Shares Among Youths and Adults 1979-1993 (1996); Tobacco Use Among U.S. Racial/Ethnic Minority Groups; Exhibited and Exposed: Annotations to Documents Discussed in Minnesota et al Plaintiffs v. Philip Morris et al Defendants; Tricks of the Tobacco Trade (1998)
    - Cigarette publications binder Vol. 11, 2002-2004; 2 folders (Box 37)
      Exposing Mr. Butts Tricks of the Trade (2002); How Cigarette Advertising Works: Rich Imagery and Poor Information (2002); Zebras in Russia! Where Next?; Targeting of Asian Americans and Pacific Islanders by the tobacco industry: results from the Minnesota Tobacco Document Repository (2002); A premier example of the illusion of harm reduction cigarettes in the 1990s (2003); Countering the Advertising of Addiction: Legislating Restrictions to Cigarette Advertising in Canada (2002); A Premier (tm) Example of Cigarette New Product Development and Unfulfilled Promises: Bullshit and Ruses (2003); The Kool Content from Advertising and Tobacco Trade Sources and Sundry Chronological Notes (2003); On Marketing "Light" and Mild Cigarettes (2003); Disclosures in the Trial Documents; Un exemple flagrant de la promesse illusoire de la reduction des dommages de la cigarette au cours des annees 1990 (2002); Expert report of Richard W. Pollay; Smoking in Movies and TV Shows (2006); Taking ad-Vantage of lax advertising regulation in the USA and Canada: Reassuring and distracting health-concerned smokers (2006)
    - Dying Art of Cigarette Promotion, circa 1997; 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Point of Sale (POS) Advertising of Cigarettes: Functions, Management and Consequences, 2004 (Box 38)
    - Working Papers Binder 1, 1987-1989; 2 folders (Box 38)
      Filters, Flavors and Flim-Flam Too! Notes on the History of Cigarette Advertising (1988); 87.1: Themes and Tactics in Cigarette Advertising 1938-1983; 87.2: Chronological Notes on the History of Cigarette Advertising; 88.1a: Promotion and Policy for a Pandemic Product; 88.1b: Notes about the History of Cigarette Advertising; 89.1: On Misleading Studies "Proving" that Cigarette Ad Bans Don't Work
    - Working Papers Binder 2, 1990; 2 folders (Box 38)
      90.1: A Scientific Smoke Screen; 90.2: More Chronological Notes on the Promotion of Cigarettes; 90.3: International Promotion of Cigarettes: An Annotated Bibliography
    - Working Papers Binder 3, 1990-1992; 2 folders (Box 38)
      90.4: Black and White and Read All Over: Cigarette Advertising in Ebony and Life; 90.5: Cigarette Health Risk Misperceptions Among Americans and Canadians; 91.1: Cigarettes Through the Advertising Ages 1950-1959; 91.2: Cigarettes Through the Advertising Ages 1960-1964; 91.3: Cigarettes Through the Advertising Ages 1965-1969; 92.1: Cigarettes Through the Advertising Ages 1970-1974; 92.2: The Tides of Tobacco Advertising 1935-1956; 92.3: Cigarette Ad Exposure to Youth: TV Use under Self-Regulation 1963; 92.4: HIstorical Content Analysis of Cigarette Advertising
    - Working Papers Binder 4, 1991-1992 (Box 38)
      Cigarettes Through the Advertising Ages; The Tides of Tobacco Advertising
    - Working Papers Binder 4, 1991-1992; 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Working Papers Binder 5, 1993 (Box 39)
      93.1: Printers Ink and Tobacco Tar 1950-1954; 93.2: Printers Ink and Tobacco Tar 1955-1959; 93.3: Cigarette Advertising and LIFE 1937-1947; 93.4: Printers Ink and Tobacco Tar 1960-1963; 93.5: Getting Good and Being Super Bad: Chapters in the Promotion of Cigarettes to Blacks
    - Working Papers Binder 6, 1994 (Box 39)
      94.1: Sifting the Ashes: An Intellectual History of Cigarette Advertising Research 1987-1993; 94.2: Consumer Reports on Cigarettes 1936-1993; 94.3: Advertising Issues in the Tobacco Journals 1950-1954; 94.4: As Anyone Can Plainly See: Brand Imagery in Cigarette Packaging and Promotion; 94.5: Stop and Think! Consider this before you develop retail cigarette warnings; 94.6: Kids, Baseball and the Marlboro Man; 94.7: Printers Ink and Tobacco Tar 1964-1970; 94.8: Advertising Issues in the Tobacco Journals 1955-1959
    - Working Papers Binder 7, 1994 (Box 39)
      94.10: Advertising and Selling the Tobacco Industry 1948-1953; 94.11: Advertising and Selling the Tobacco Industry 1954-1958; 94.12: Printers Ink and Tobacco Tar 1933-1949; 94.13: Advertisng Issues in the Tobacco Journals 1960-1962; 94.14: Advertisng Issues in the Tobacco Journals 1963-1965
    - Working Papers Binder 8, 1995; 2 folders (Box 39)